zoostores.com 2013-09-23

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to Zoostores.com. The Privacy Notice describes the information we gather about you and the purpose for which it is used.

You may interact with our site in one of two ways: contacting us by email or placing an order. The kinds of personal information that we may collect during these interactions include: name, address, email address, telephone number, and credit card information.

We also log certain non-personal information when you visit Zoostores.com, such as the type of browser (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer) used, the type of operating system (e.g., Windows XP, Mac OSX) used, and the domain of your Internet service provider (e.g., Earthlink, AOL, MSN). We log this information using 'cookies,' which are small data text files that Web sites store on your computer's hard drive if your Web browser permits. Cookies, which can later be retrieved to identify you to Zoostores.com, make your use of our site easier, allow you to retrieve earlier shopping carts, and help us to maintain a secure site. **For your safety, you will be unable to shop on our site if your browser is not set to accept cookies.**

We only use or disclose to third parties the information you provide about yourself to fulfill an order, to enroll you in services you have requested, to respond to your inquiries, to request your feedback/review of your order experience or product, or to offer you related products or services. We do not rent or sell customer data.

We use the non-personal information we collect to analyze the overall traffic on our site. This analysis helps us make site design changes to improve your experience.

We may disclose the personal information you provide in response to a particular legal process (e.g., court order, subpoena, law enforcement agency's request).

We require that Agents and Partners of Zoostores.com who have access to your personal information protect this information according to their stated Privacy Policies – or, in the event these Agents and Partners of Zoostores.com have no stated Privacy Policy, according to this Privacy Notice. They may only use the personal information you provide to carry out the services they are performing for Zoostores.com (e.g., fulfillment of your order or enrollment in services you have requested).

Zoostores.com uses several of the latest encryption technologies to keep your personal information safe. Your private ordering information – including your credit card number – is encrypted using several keys for maximum security. Your credit card and billing information cannot be poached as it travels through our ordering system (128-bit SSL encryption), and the numbers are unreadable to anyone trying to access the site remotely. We have implemented the requisite physical, electronic, and managerial processes to prevent unauthorized access and maintain data security.

You may contact us at any time to update the information we have about you. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us, either by email, postal mail, or phone, please let us know by sending us an email.

Please note that such requests may take up to 6-8 weeks to become effective. Please also note that when you make a purchase, we will send you emails to confirm your order and may also need to contact you by phone, mail, or email if we have other questions regarding your order.
